♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll reset it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
(SCREAMING)
Was that you screaming, huh?
It’s a…
(CRYING)
What the...
Sissi? What’s all this about?
It’s Aelita Stones, Jim…
She isn’t feeling well.
What about you, you’re not sleeping?
Me? Uh, well…
She… Woke me uh-uh-up.
Aelita? What’s going on?
It’s… nothing.
Okay, go back to bed everybody. Go on.
It was daytime, there were
these men-in-black coming after me.
It was horrible.
You must have had a nightmare.
You shouldn’t get worked out, it happens to everyone.
Yeah, that’s right. Happens to me all of the time.
One night, I dreamt I was on a date with Sissi.
Can you think of a worse dream?
Speaking of which, how’s your internet dating going Odd?
Great. There’s this fantastic girl that I really flipped over too.
And I just found out she’s a student right here at Kadic Academy.
It’s totally crazy.
I see her everyday, and I have no idea who she is.
And what’s worse he stayed up all night
exchanging chat messages with her.
I didn’t sleep at all thanks to him.
She sends me these messages that are so romantic,
I mean like poems. Listen to this.
Love is not looking at one another--
It’s looking together in the same direction, huh?
Hey! How do you know that?
It’s a poem by the guy who wrote the Little Prince,
she may be romantic but she’s not very original.
Okay, it’s time to get wet.
Are you gonna cut swimming again Einstein, huh?
No, I can’t.
Jim has already warned me.
No more dumb excuses here.
Great! We finally get to see that buff athletic body of yours.
I can’t wait.
You may be surprised.
The human body is made up of 90% water. And that is why it floats.
Because contrary to what you might think, water floats.
Don’t forget Archmedes principle.
Any body plunged into a liquid eh…
is…
ehh…
Comes out wet?
Yeah right. No, that’s not it.
Now, no-one has to be scared of the water.
Unless of course you’re lost at sea,
somewhere in the middle of the Indian Ocean.
In that case, you would certainly have the right to be say
”Wow that’s a lot of water there”--
Tanamiya. I know it!
Yeah sure, it’s Sophie.
She kinda fits the profile of all those chat messages.
What makes you think it’s a girl in our class?
It might just as easily be Milly or Tamiya.
Which reminds me of when I was a salvage diver.
You used to be a salvage diver, Jim?
I’d rather not talk about it.
Azra? No…
No way, she’s not a first year student either I forgot.
Maybe she’s in Yumi’s class.
Haha, what if it’s Anais Fiquet Annies Fighet?
Next to her you’re real shrimp.
Stern and Della Robbia,
I’m sorry if I’m boring you.
Alright, on deck.
Let’s what you can do.
You okay?
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
Aelita!
This time it was much more detailed.
There were still the men in black,
but I was at the Hermitage.
The doctor said you passed out from the cold.
That may be, but what about the visions?
Where are they coming from Jeremie?
I haven’t the slightest idea.
Although I’m sure that it’s no big deal.
The best thing is for you to get some rest now.
We’ll talk about it later.
Right, I’ve gotta go. I’m already late.
Us too, Mrs. Hertz is gonna kill us.
Wait a minute, I’m just about to find out who she is.
Come on Odd, you can
talk to your cyborg girlfriend after class.
Take the computer with you.
Thanks.
See you in a bit Aelita, I’ll come back
again to check on you after science.
Hey!
Can’t you look where you’re going you clumsy dork?
Oh, sorry Sissi.
I mistook you for a doorpost, ha.
Hey! She’s in our class.
She said that she has science now with Mrs. Hertz.
Odd, pass me the computer. I forgot to check something.
Settle down and be quiet, please. Open your books to page 99.
Oh no… An activated tower.
Ma’am, can I go to the bathroom?
Uh Me too.
--Uh Me too.
Oh no you don’t!
It’s always the same with you three. You should’ve gone before class.
And put that computer away before I take it away!
Mercury freezes at 38 degrees below zero celsius.
At room temperature it is therefore in a liquid state.
We use it in certain devices such as thermometers
for instance because it expands with heat.
(PIANO MUSIC PLAYS: TWINKLE TWINKLE LITTLE STAR)
Calm down Aelita.
It’s also a very heavy metal.
Which means, what? Sissi?
It means…
That a pound of metal weighs, nearly a ton?
(LAUGHTER)
(BELL RINGS)
Warn Yumi.
I’ll go get Aelita.
We’ll meet up at the Factory.
Calm down.
Aelita?
(PHONE RINGS)
Jeremie?
Aelita? Where are you?
At the Hermitage.
But you should be resting.
These vision are haunting me. I’ve got to know where they’re coming from.
Right. Anyway, listen. You’ve ought to know that Xana’s on the offensive.
The others are already at the Factory. Don’t move, I’ll come and get you.
I’m big enough to make it to the Factory by myself.
Okay, but hurry!
Aelita. Come, quickly!
Hello? Is anyone there?
This way.
Just 30 seconds more and you can +head for the scanners.
What’s Aelita up to?
She said she’d be right over. I should have gone to pick her up.
Ah, there you are at last.
Hey Cinderella, we said midnight on the dot.
Aelita. Are you okay?
I had some more visions.
I saw a man, and he was--
Who?
Franz Hopper.
Huh, are you sure?
I know it sounds crazy, but I’m sure it was him.
What if this is Xana’s offensive?
What?
I mean, these strange visions.
Exactly. Xana is perfectly capable of stimulating your cerebral cortex,
through the virus that links you to him.
And from that he can paradoxically simulate in you an artificial sleep
and involuntary psychic activity that goes with it.
In short, you mean Xana’s showing you free movies.
But why?
Let’s not hang around to find out.
Let’s go deactivate the tower.
Ulrich and Odd first.
Transfer Odd.
Transfer Ulrich.
Scanner Odd.
Scanner Ulrich.
Virtualization!
The activated tower is due South.
Here come your vehicles.
Virtualization!
Okay, you’re all there now. Don’t waste any time.
Coming Aelita?
Xana’s monsters up ahead. You see them?
We’d have to be as near-sighted as you not to see them.
Odd, you handle the Bloks.
Yumi and I will take care of the Tarantulas.
You got it.
Ground and air attack.
Piece of cake.
What’s going on?
The transporter! But I didn’t call it up.
Aelita! What are you doing?
Sorry Jeremie, but I want some answers.
I have to find out where these visions are coming from.
Aelita don’t do it it’s a trap!
Way to go Yumi.
Xana’s succeeded, Aelita’s going to Sector 5.
You have to get there fast.
Holosphere system connected.
Okay.
The corridor’s still there.
That’s because the countdown is still ticking, hurry!
Oh no! Aelita!
The Scyphozoa is taking over Aelita’s memory!
We’re almost there.
Great. A leapfrog contest.
There’s only one way. One, two, three!
Hurry up!
You think this is easy?
At this rate, we’ll never make it in time.
Odd mind telling me what you’re doing?
Saving the day.
Yes!
Odd!
Odd? Are you okay?
Sector Five is even worse than Mrs. Hertz’s class.
Only ten seconds before the end of the countdown.
Let’s go princess.
Here comes the elevator. Now.
As soon as you get to the Celestial Dome,
get out of Sector Five and head for the Desert sector fast!
Okay Aelita?
Aelita! What did I tell you?
We’re not getting any data.
You have to deactivate the tower.
Aelita!
This will only take a few seconds.
It’s one of Xana’s traps Aelita!
He created these visions to lure you over to Sector Five.
Give me the controls.
Did you hear me? Aelita!
Ulrich, Yumi, drag her out of there by force.
What do you want us to do? Knock her out?
It won’t be necessary.
I’m sure I find what I’m looking for.
Aelita.
Even if do find the origin of these visions,
what’s the point if Xana takes your memory away from you?
I’m almost there.
Yumi, Ulrich, we got trouble.
The Scyphozoa’s got Aelita.
We gotta deal with the Flying Mantas first.
Yeah!
Hurry up! Aelita’s about to lose all of her memory!
You okay Aelita?
It’s time you deactivated the tower.
The tunnel’s open.
(CELESTIAL MUSIC)
Tower deactivated.
Hi Aelita. Well, any more visions?
Gone.
You see?
It was just a trap, made in Xana.
I guess. But I still would’ve really
liked to know where those memories came from.
I think that Xana must have made the whole thing up.
Or maybe the memories came from someone else.
Implanted in you by Xana in order to scare you.
That could be it.
It’s very strange though.
I was really under the impression
that I was reliving the events I was seeing.
That however, can’t be.
Yes, I know.
So Odd, how’s your cyber sweetheart?
She’s too cool! I really have got it bad this time guys.
I’m gonna meet her.
When?
Now! At the vending machines. Later.
I don’t believe this.
So Odd, your fantastic girl. What’s she like?
Uh, surprising.
So. Did your meet your mystery computer boyfriend, what’s he like?
If he’s a mystery why would I tell you, you dork?
What’s the matter with you?
You act as if you’ve never saw me before.
Never like that.
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY THE FOXTROT FANATICS